<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer</id>
  <title>iceagefarmer Telegram archive</title>

  <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer" rel="alternate"/>
  <generator>tg-archive 1.3.0</generator>
  <subtitle>&lt;br&gt;Telegram archive&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class="github-url" style="display:inline"&gt;(&lt;a href="https://github.com/milahu/iceagefarmer"&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/div&gt;</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-12.html#3270</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-12-25 15:05:45+00:00 (#3270)</title>

    <content type="html">Wherever you are, whatever you’re navigating, may this season bring a spark of clarity and a reminder that the light is still here, even when the world feels upside‑down.

And that light doesn’t need perfect conditions to shine…

Merry Christmas and a steady heart to you all!</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-12.html#3270"/>
    <published>2025-12-25T15:05:45+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3269</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-11-24 13:49:25+00:00 (#3269)</title>

    <content type="html">GOING VIRAL: a leaked video shows Campbell’s Soup VP admitting their soup is “gross” and contains “bioengineered meat," and is unhealthy "shit for poor people."

I’ve warned about this trash for years — now an insider is caught saying he wouldn’t eat his own product.

"I don't want to eat some 3-d printed fake chicken trash!"

Yeah.  Neither do we.

 ... when the system itself no longer believes its own lies, consensus reality is no longer consensual. Break the entrainment.

- @iceagefarmer

#WarOnMeat</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3269"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3269.mp4"/>
    <published>2025-11-24T13:49:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3268</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-11-22 08:53:02+00:00 (#3268)</title>

    <content type="html">COP30 goes up in flames.

As delegates from across the globe gathered to advance the technocratic agenda at COP30, the venue literally went up in flames.  Thirteen were hospitalized for smoke inhalation, and negotiations collapsed.

Just as their agenda is crashing and burning (even Gates jumping ship), so too now are their rituals of performative "climate consensus."

https://www.channelnewsasia.com/world/cop30-climate-summit-evacuated-after-fire-disrupts-negotiations-5480851</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3268"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.channelnewsasia.com/world/cop30-climate-summit-evacuated-after-fire-disrupts-negotiations-5480851"/>
    <published>2025-11-22T08:53:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3267</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-11-20 14:43:28+00:00 (#3267)</title>

    <content type="html">Worth noticing: Israeli startup Remilk is launching New Milk, a low-sugar, lactose-free milk featuring recombinant dairy proteins made in fermentation tanks, rather than from cows.

The product, rolling out in cafés and restaurants across Israel this week and hitting major retailers nationwide next month.

CEO Aviv Wolff claims, "It gives you the same experience as traditional dairy without the downsides," having burned $150M to engineer a strain of yeast that spits out beta-lactoglobulin.

Oh, and they claim it's kosher.  🤡

This is the next phase of technocratic food: reality replaced by simulation, fermentation tanks standing in for cows, proteins stripped from context and sold as “progress.”

https://agfundernews.com/new-milk-signals-new-phase-for-recombinant-dairy-says-remilk-it-doesnt-look-like-another-alternative-product</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3267"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://agfundernews.com/new-milk-signals-new-phase-for-recombinant-dairy-says-remilk-it-doesnt-look-like-another-alternative-product"/>
    <published>2025-11-20T14:43:28+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3266</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-11-20 14:35:14+00:00 (#3266)</title>

    <content type="html">Microsoft now owns the farm’s data

Land O'Lakes has partnered with Microsoft, handing over its decades of farm-level ag data to Azure AI Foundry, wrapped inside a new “digital assistant” called Oz.

The pitch: optimization and risk mitigation.
The reality: soil becomes data, farmers become operators, decisions mediated by algorithms.

The empire/technocrats seek to quantify and control every aspect of reality. But the harder they squeeze, the squishier reality becomes, slipping through their fingers...

https://agnewswire.com/2025/11/12/land-olakes-and-microsoft-partner-to-accelerate-ai-innovation-in-agriculture/

#ai #WarOnFarms</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3266"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://agnewswire.com/2025/11/12/land-olakes-and-microsoft-partner-to-accelerate-ai-innovation-in-agriculture/"/>
    <published>2025-11-20T14:35:14+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3265</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-11-20 14:24:47+00:00 (#3265)</title>

    <content type="html">Got debt?  Just erase it.

Fake meat company "Meati" has spun off a shell company "Meati Holdings," selling its mycelium-based fermentation technology to the new holding company, and then defaulting on all their debt — walking away with a clean slate.

This kind of financial wizardry (once known as FRAUD) is how companies implementing the technocratic agenda are kept alive.

BeyondMeat is working through a similar process right now, completely screwing their investors — a small price to pay to continue executing on the WEF/UN SDGs.

https://agfundernews.com/new-owner-now-controls-meati-debt-free-rebranding-planned-in-2026

#WarOnMeat</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3265"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://agfundernews.com/new-owner-now-controls-meati-debt-free-rebranding-planned-in-2026"/>
    <published>2025-11-20T14:24:47+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3264</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-11-17 22:08:30+00:00 (#3264)</title>

    <content type="html">Registration precedes confiscation...

Italy floats a one‑time 52% tax on private gold holdings:

Something tells me there are going to be a few tragic boat accidents in the near future.

https://www.kitco.com/news/article/2025-11-17/italy-considers-one-time-52-tax-cut-private-gold-holdings</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3264"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.kitco.com/news/article/2025-11-17/italy-considers-one-time-52-tax-cut-private-gold-holdings"/>
    <published>2025-11-17T22:08:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3263</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-11-12 09:08:32+00:00 (#3263)</title>

    <content type="html">Bill Gates’ new $1.4B soil bioengineering initiative, sold under the guise of “philanthropic climate adaptation,” is an effort to hijack the biosphere itself:  soil mapping, engineered microbes, and genetic interventions under the banner of sustainability.

Jon Fleetwood nails it.  His reporting aligns with what I’ve been saying:  these aren’t isolated ag-tech projects. They’re nodes in a larger planetary bio‑surveillance grid, a system designed to monitor, record, and ultimately control life at every level, from crops and forests to human microbiomes.

👉 Jon's Coverage: https://jonfleetwood.substack.com/p/bill-gates-launches-14-billion-soil

👉 My analysis: https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/the-planetary-bio-surveillance-grid

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3263"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://jonfleetwood.substack.com/p/bill-gates-launches-14-billion-soil"/>
    <published>2025-11-12T09:08:32+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3262</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-11-12 09:06:02+00:00 (#3262)</title>

    <content type="html">New post:  "The Collapse of Meaning"

In a world awash in algorithmic feeds and AI slop, language and symbols are losing their meaning.  This is by design.  The technocrats are engaged in ontological warfare.

👉 https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/the-collapse-of-meaning

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3262"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/the-collapse-of-meaning"/>
    <published>2025-11-12T09:06:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3261</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-11-07 10:19:33+00:00 (#3261)</title>

    <content type="html">And if you missed the report on "Absolute Zero," it's here — 5 years ago but evergreen:
     https://www.bitchute.com/video/tZiN3ZKP4LNW</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3261"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.bitchute.com/video/tZiN3ZKP4LNW"/>
    <published>2025-11-07T10:19:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3260</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-11-07 10:19:16+00:00 (#3260)</title>

    <content type="html">The technocratic agenda is unfolding apace!  Are you seeing it, or did you get pulled into their crisis narratives?

✈️ Domestic flights cut by 10% in the U.S. this week, framed as a temporary shutdown response...but mirrors France's ban on short-haul flights.

🚛 Calls for trucking reform are increasing after crashes of illegal drivers were made high-profile by the news — problem, reaction, technocratic solution....

🚢 Shipping insurance premiums are exploding, with some routes now costing up to $1M per trip to cover.

🔥 Gas boilers banned in new UK homes starting next year under Future Homes Standard.

🥩 Meat excluded from Catalonia's UBI pilot diets:  no beef or lamb, by design.

🏗 Construction in UK restricted to “absolutely necessary” projects, with electrified processes mandated.

💸 UBI pilots expanding globally: free money... but programmable, conditional, and only for "compliant citizens..."

In other words, the system is implementing MASSIVE CHANGE -- RIGHT NOW, but instead of fighting it, everyone is too busy blaming the other side for the shutdown. Or thinking that "nation states" are going to war. If you still believe there are sovereign countries after seeing the entire planet lock down, I got news for you: it's a facade, being maintained just as long as it provides cover to bring in the new systems.

Once those facades of left/right or nation states are no longer advantageous to the technocrats, they will fall. No sooner.

Keep your eye on the big picture. These crises are real—don't ignore them—but don't get lost in the noise.  This is all by design.

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-11.html#3260"/>
    <published>2025-11-07T10:19:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-10.html#3259</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-10-27 14:35:24+00:00 (#3259)</title>

    <content type="html">I was poisoned by an antibiotic.

Despite black box warnings, fluoroquinolone antibiotics like Cipro and Levaquin are still prescribed 14+ million times a year, harming millions.  Many are left permanently disabled, in wheelchairs, or in their grave.

This exposé dives into the science, the damage, and the staggering human cost.  If my writing this (or your sharing it) helps even one person avoid these drugs, it’s well worth it.

https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/fluoroquinolones-prescribed-poisons</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-10.html#3259"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/fluoroquinolones-prescribed-poisons"/>
    <published>2025-10-27T14:35:24+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-10.html#3258</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-10-01 19:54:14+00:00 (#3258)</title>

    <content type="html">🚨 Ignore the rhetoric. Watch the patterns:

French army chief says public must be ready for high-intensity warfare—tonight.  Hospital wards are being prepped (France, Germany, Switzerland, Poland, Estonia and Latvia). Train after train rolls east with heavy armor. Drone incursion theatrics are labeled false flags by Russia, with rumors Ukraine is planning an even bigger false flag swirling.

Trump greenlights long-range strikes into Russia. Gold and silver are spiking.

The Vaccine passport Digital ID rollout has been met with a lackluster response, so they’ll flip the table. A complete collapse the West — like that the Deagle predictions describe — is not inconceivable.  For each of DoD, ARPA-H, Palantir/Ginkgo, there is a mirror copy in China/BRICS, equally ready to be deployed after what may lay ahead.

A giant, protracted war offers escape from broken economies and perfect leverage for installing biometric controls and digital rationing, a permanent surveillance state that will never roll back "afterwards."

The Overton window may not have caught up with these recent escalations, but the pattern is clear.

Prepare accordingly.  🙏

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-10.html#3258"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://demstate.com/article/gen-pierre-schill-urges-french-army-to-prepare-for-high-intensity-warfare"/>
    <published>2025-10-01T19:54:14+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3257</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-29 14:24:02+00:00 (#3257)</title>

    <content type="html">Global Emissions Surveillance &amp; Digital Product Passports

“What Christian is describing is the ‘full spectrum dominance’ that carbon monopoly players needed to make the board fully functional. No escape, no loopholes.”

  💯% !

The system is already watching and recording.  See for yourself:

👉  https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/global-emissions-surveillance-and</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3257"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3257.mp4"/>
    <published>2025-09-29T14:24:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3256</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-28 20:57:25+00:00 (#3256)</title>

    <content type="html">Critical intel here — this is how the carbon rationing actually works.

Global Emissions Surveillance &amp; Digital Product Passports

Climate TRACE tracks emissions from over 660 million sources in near real-time. That data is already flowing into supply chains, digital product passports, and carbon scoring systems, enabling enforcement on farmers, landowners, and consumers.

This video breaks down the architecture of control that’s already online.

YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uAqFQm09dB4
Substack: https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/global-emissions-surveillance-and

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3256"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uAqFQm09dB4"/>
    <published>2025-09-28T20:57:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3255</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-26 17:11:00+00:00 (#3255)</title>

    <content type="html">"De-extinction company" Colossal Biosciences has announced that they successfully gene-edited primordial germ cells (PGCs) from a pigeon.  Cloning/editing genes of birds is harder than mammals, wherein scientists take an unfertilized egg, remove its nucleus and replace it with the nucleus from a donor body.  Birds’ large, opaque eggs, on the other hand, are laid after embryos begin developing, which complicates the approach.

Instead, Colossal plans to inject gene-edited Nicobar germ cells into chicken embryos. These altered chickens would grow up with pigeon-making cells in their ovaries or testes, acting like surrogates. Thus, such a chicken could lay an egg that hatches a pigeon and, after additional gene edits, potentially a dodo-like bird.

and ... they dress it up in "saving the animals" altruism:

“By developing these protocols,” Shapiro said in the press release, “we’re establishing crucial biobanking capabilities and opening new possibilities for genetic rescue of endangered species.”

Honestly, this is like watching a 5-year old play with a nuclear bomb.  These scientists have no idea the ramifications of the technology with which they are playing.  It will not end well — and you can take that to the biobank.

- @iceagefarmer

https://www.dallasnews.com/news/2025/09/19/resurrection-of-dodo-bird-one-step-closer-thanks-to-transformative-tool-says-colossal/</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3255"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.dallasnews.com/news/2025/09/19/resurrection-of-dodo-bird-one-step-closer-thanks-to-transformative-tool-says-colossal/"/>
    <published>2025-09-26T17:11:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3254</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-26 14:49:09+00:00 (#3254)</title>

    <content type="html">Feels like this may be a deliberate attempt to ignite the UK.  They know how unpopular the digital ID idea is, having gathered that data when floating vaccine passports. Lord knows they’ve been doing everything else they can to get a reaction out of people.

At any rate, anyone who was waiting to start building/supporting a parallel economy:  time to get to work!

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3254"/>
    <published>2025-09-26T14:49:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3253</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-26 14:27:51+00:00 (#3253)</title>

    <content type="html">"If you were looking for a hill to die on, it might as well be this one.

"Brit Card makes possible the tracking of your movements, what you post online, what protests you might attend, how you spend your money, and all of that data is stored forever. There would be no state-sanctioned opt-out... All citizens would become digitally visible to the state across every transaction.

"What happens if you refuse to comply with some or other future diktat? Will you lose access to your funds? Will you lose your freedom to move? BritCard makes privacy itself is impossible—forbidden, in fact.

"If we let this happen, then all of the mechanisms for totalitarianism are handed to government, and to the transnational corporations, and unelected bureaucracies, and three-letter agencies pulling their strings.

"By means such as this, the rights our predecessors fought and died for are transformed into privileges we may or may not be granted conditional upon every aspect of our behaviour."

via Neil Oliver, X: @thecoastguy</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3253"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3253.mp4"/>
    <published>2025-09-26T14:27:51+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3252</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-26 14:17:06+00:00 (#3252)</title>

    <content type="html">UK/Palantir to "Transform Lethality", Accelerate "Kill Chain"

The UK's new strategic partnership with Palantir is pretty wild — straight from gov.uk:

Palantir and the UK military will work together to "transform lethality on the battlefield", supporting the development of data and AI-powered capabilities across data analysis, intelligence, decision support and targeting systems.

They specifically mention a "kill chain" for "faster options for attacking an enemy target."

... and the deal extends beyond AI on the battlefield. It also mentions Palantir will do pro bono (free!) mentoring to British companies — because it's not about the profit. It's about the data.

on YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YYb6P2rr140
on Substack: https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/ukpalantir-to-transform-lethality

https://www.iceagefarmer.com/2025/09/26/uk-palantir-to-transform-lethality-accelerate-kill-chain/</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3252"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YYb6P2rr140"/>
    <published>2025-09-26T14:17:06+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3251</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-26 14:15:23+00:00 (#3251)</title>

    <content type="html">YouTube claims they have stopped censoring — let's find out!

New channel is here, if you dare...

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCu6ji73lNjrvewfkiUaJ2UQ</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3251"/>
    <published>2025-09-26T14:15:23+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3250</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-26 13:55:58+00:00 (#3250)</title>

    <content type="html">Mark of the Beast?  UK now requiring Digital ID to work.

Naturally it's to "secure the border" that they've deliberately eroded (classic problem-reaction-solution).

Expect to see an explosion of black markets, underground labor as people resist this digital ID.  If the global AI surveillance system is the beast, then there is no denying, this is its mark.

https://www.theguardian.com/politics/live/2025/sep/26/keir-starmer-digital-id-cards-immigration-borders-reform-uk-politics-live</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3250"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.theguardian.com/politics/live/2025/sep/26/keir-starmer-digital-id-cards-immigration-borders-reform-uk-politics-live"/>
    <published>2025-09-26T13:55:58+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3249</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-24 06:43:59+00:00 (#3249)</title>

    <content type="html">Building the Beast System: Microbes, AI &amp; Total Surveillance [NEW VIDEO]

The genetically engineered microbes discussed in Part One of this report aren’t just wiping out the natural biosphere to fix nitrogen.

In this video we’ll explore the DOD’s Tellus project that offers a blueprint to the microbial architecture of the global bio-surveillance system, and how this design has been implemented and is now being deployed.

👉 FULL VIDEO: https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/building-the-beast-system-microbes

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3249"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3249.mp4"/>
    <published>2025-09-24T06:43:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3248</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-23 19:10:11+00:00 (#3248)</title>

    <content type="html">UK proposes farmers should do more with less:

A new 30/50/50 plan — boost output by 30% &amp; halve emissions, by 2050.

One official explains, "Our over-precautionary and under-resourced regulatory processes are stifling access to farming innovations which are readily available to producers elsewhere," he said.

That statement suggests aggressively adopting "innovations" (like the synthetic microbes that are being given liability protection) — and more resources to regulate traditional farming out of business.

https://www.farminguk.com/news/westminster-to-hear-farming-blueprint-to-produce-more-from-less-_67260.html</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3248"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.farminguk.com/news/westminster-to-hear-farming-blueprint-to-produce-more-from-less-_67260.html"/>
    <published>2025-09-23T19:10:11+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3247</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-23 13:21:49+00:00 (#3247)</title>

    <content type="html">Spying on Farmers?  the Global Carbon Compliance Grid:

Years ago I covered an Al Gore-backed project called Climate TRACE, which promised to fuse satellite data and other data sources using AI to "detect greenhouse gas emissions" anywhere in the world.  "So we can track down that last cow fart!"

Now, the data is live, and public, with resolution down to 1km².  That means:

- Emissions from individual buildings can be tracked
- Fertilizer application — especially nitrogen (which they want to ban!) — can be inferred from spectral analysis
- CROPS can be identified, field by field.

And what's crazy is, not only are they spying on every square kilometer on earth, they are publishing the data for anyone to look at.  That means Climate TRACE needn't bother with enforcement; that is left to governments, insurers, or ESG-based funding.  Automated fines or denying funding is a mere flip of a switch from here.

BOTTOM LINE:  the mechanism to enforce the carbon emissions or fertilizer restrictions that WEF et al are discussing is already in place.

https://climatetrace.org/data

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3247"/>
    <published>2025-09-23T13:21:49+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3246</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-19 23:33:21+00:00 (#3246)</title>

    <content type="html">photo_2025-09-19_23-33-21.jpg</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3246"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3246.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-09-19T23:33:21+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3245</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-19 23:33:21+00:00 (#3245)</title>

    <content type="html">The UK's new strategic partnership with Palantir is pretty wild — straight from gov.uk:

Palantir and the UK military will work together to "transform lethality on the battlefield", supporting the development of data and AI-powered capabilities across data analysis, intelligence, decision support and targeting systems.

They specifically mention a "kill chain" for "faster options for attacking an enemy target."

... and the deal extends beyond AI on the battlefield. It also mentions Palantir will do pro bono (free!) mentoring to British companies — because it's not about the profit.  It's about the data.

- @iceagefarmer

https://www.gov.uk/government/news/new-strategic-partnership-to-unlock-billions-and-boost-military-ai-and-innovation</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3245"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3245.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-09-19T23:33:21+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3244</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-19 23:18:51+00:00 (#3244)</title>

    <content type="html">AI Infrastructure Investment:  such a clever euphemism for big tech companies moving in to take over the UK.  (And same words Trump used on his day 2:  "the biggest AI infrastructure project by far in history" to build "big beautiful data centers...")

The Tech Prosperity Deal's £31bn "investment" is actually an invasion:  the fact that they call it "Infrastructure" reinforces that this isn't about investment or innovation.  This is "critical infrastructure" to build out the planetary surveillance grid.

Not mentioned in the BBC's coverage is that Palantir also penned a deal with the UK Ministry of Defense (MoD) ... see next post.

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3244"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c7016ljre03o"/>
    <published>2025-09-19T23:18:51+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3243</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-15 10:06:43+00:00 (#3243)</title>

    <content type="html">Albania appoints AI minister to government to be "free of corruption."  This is exactly the plan elucidated over a decade ago:  ruin governments and collapse society until people demand an AI rescue (where the AI is administered by the technocrats, naturally).

And it's happening.  Now.  Just look around.

Oh, and indeed — the AI was created by Microsoft.  This isn't a product or a new application to increase trust — it's a takeover of institutions by anti-human forces.

https://apnews.com/article/albania-new-cabinet-parliament-ai-minister-diella-corruption-5e53c5d5973ff0e4c8f009ab3f78f369</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3243"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://apnews.com/article/albania-new-cabinet-parliament-ai-minister-diella-corruption-5e53c5d5973ff0e4c8f009ab3f78f369"/>
    <published>2025-09-15T10:06:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3242</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-09 23:52:12+00:00 (#3242)</title>

    <content type="html">NEW VIDEO: The Biotech Coup: Microbes to Rule the World

There is an active effort to modify the substrate of life on our planet: to recolonize the very soil on the surface of the Earth with genetically engineered microbes. Millions of acres of U.S. farmland have already been inoculated.

The soil itself is being re-formatted from a natural ecosystem into a patent-pending, CRISPR-modified, nitrogen-fixing, Roundup-spittin’ machine — with consideration given neither to crops nor consumer.

Let's talk about it:

https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/the-biotech-coup-microbes-to-rule

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3242"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/the-biotech-coup-microbes-to-rule"/>
    <published>2025-09-09T23:52:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3241</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-09 13:09:48+00:00 (#3241)</title>

    <content type="html">40% US Farms forecast to go bankrupt!?  US Agriculture going over a cliff

“Farmers are literally losing money per acre while Big Agriculture is making hundreds of millions of dollars and more.”

Chairman of the Arkansas Rice Growers Association — and 50-year career farmer — says there is a “coming disaster” unlike anything he’s witnessed, “I’ve never seen this kinda look in farmers’ eyes. It’s fear. And it’s based in undeniable facts.”  "Whether this year or next year or the next, there’s a crash coming."

"In a nutshell, we are going over a cliff. Banks are forecasting farm bankruptcies at 25% to 40%, and the dirty secret is out. Everyone knows it; everyone feels it.”

“And the solution is supposedly another bailout or a gap payment the following year? Wake the hell up: Where do you think that money is gonna go? It won’t go to farmers."  It goes straight to the Big Ag monopolies.

Bailey Buffalo, 6th-generation farmer, is calling it quits: "Some blame the current president. Some blame the last president. Nobody is looking at where farmers spend their money. Farmers pay monopolies &amp; have no choice."

(source)

Grow your garden.  Support your local farmers &amp; producers.  Build resilient alternative systems.

- @iceagefarmer

#WarOnFarms</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3241"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.agweb.com/markets/outraged-farmers-blame-ag-monopolies-catastrophic-collapse-looms"/>
    <published>2025-09-09T13:09:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3240</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-09 11:10:52+00:00 (#3240)</title>

    <content type="html">AlterEgo: unveiled yesterday, can directly read brain activity, allowing you to use thoughts to dictate text, takes notes, send messages, and more.  The device builds on research from MIT Media Lab.

If they are unveiling this technology publicly, it's not a huge leap to imagine technology exists to read thoughts at a distance.

Thought it was crazy to have an Alexa listening to all conversations?  Why not go all the way and just give the technocrats access to your every thought...just so you can send texts in your head...</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3240"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3240.mp4"/>
    <published>2025-09-09T11:10:52+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3239</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-05 21:41:11+00:00 (#3239)</title>

    <content type="html"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3239"/>
    <published>2025-09-05T21:41:11+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3238</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-05 21:40:56+00:00 (#3238)</title>

    <content type="html">FLASHBACK: Microbiome experts to speak at World Economic Forum [2017]

Almost a decade ago the WEF was entertaining ideas about how to invisibly infiltrate our environments and our bodies.  In 2017, Davos hosted academics studying aspects of the microbiome to speak about how to manipulate the microbiome for improving human health ... or eliminate target pests.

In the 8 years since, they've made a lot of progress...

https://news.cornell.edu/stories/2017/01/microbiome-experts-speak-world-economic-forum</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3238"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3238.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-09-05T21:40:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3237</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-05 19:09:37+00:00 (#3237)</title>

    <content type="html">CONSPIRACY THEORIST

The term was invoked to discredit doubters of the Warren Report following JFK's assassination.  Here is a direct link to a source document from the CIA claiming the reputation of the US government must be protected by "countering and discrediting the claims of conspiracy theorists."

Just think:  this is 43 years before Kass Sunstein discussed "cognitive infiltration of the conspiracy community..."

https://archive.org/details/CIADOC1035960/mode/2up</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3237"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3237.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-09-05T19:09:37+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3236</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-05 17:22:46+00:00 (#3236)</title>

    <content type="html">Palantir CTO (Chief Technology Officer) Shyam Sankar is now Chairman of the Board of Ginkgo Bioworks.

Palantir/ARPA-H have effectively turned Ginkgo into their synthetic biology arm, manufacturing microbes to permeate every ecological and biological environment (ie from farms/forests to your gut) and report on their surroundings — a total planetary bio-surveillance grid.

"You can think of a cell as a computer — you put in code, and you get out product.  It is the future of manufacturing."

This is hijacking and distorting natural biology to feed data to the beast system.</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3236"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3236.mp4"/>
    <published>2025-09-05T17:22:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3235</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-05 10:47:21+00:00 (#3235)</title>

    <content type="html">Nearly perfect.  😂</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3235"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3235.mp4"/>
    <published>2025-09-05T10:47:21+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3234</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-05 10:41:01+00:00 (#3234)</title>

    <content type="html">In his book, Time Perspective and Morale, psychologist Kurt Lewin likewise encapsulate some of the fundamental principles of Tavistock’s theory of psychological warfare, describing a "strategy of terror":

"One of the main techniques for breaking morale through a ‘strategy of terror’ consists in exactly this tactic – keep the person hazy as to where he stands and just what he may expect. If in addition frequent vacillations between severe disciplinary measures and promises of good treatment together with spreading of contradictory news, make the ‘cognitive structure’ of this situation utterly unclear, then the individual may cease to even know when a particular plan would lead toward or away from his goal. Under these conditions even those who have definite goals and are ready to take risks, will be paralyzed by severe inner conflicts in regard to what to do."

The technocrats are absolutely using this technique on the public at large.  Stay focused on your own goals and resilience.  We are playing the long game.</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3234"/>
    <published>2025-09-05T10:41:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3233</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-09-01 14:57:41+00:00 (#3233)</title>

    <content type="html">The Planetary Bio-Surveillance Grid

Let's imagine a world where a faulty worldview in a mechanistic reality has given birth to a psychotic technocratic elite that seeks to monitor every aspect of reality in AI "digital twin" systems -- but the public is increasingly showing awareness of (and resistance to!) wearable IoT devices and the surveillance state. What is a future-AI-as-god-worshipping-technocrat to do?

Naturally, preferring asymmetric warfare, you change tactics and attack in an invisible way: synthetic biology. You create surveillance microbes, stage a crisis that demands their mass deployment "for your safety." You flood the zone with them, quickly replacing the natural microbiome across farms, forests, foods, guts, and wastewater. Suddenly, humanity is being monitored from within -- no wearable devices, no microchip implants. You welcome the myriad problems this disconnection from our ancestral microbiome will inevitably create, as each offers a chance to further use biotechnology and tighten your grip.

👉  FULL ARTICLE:  https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/the-planetary-bio-surveillance-grid</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-09.html#3233"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/the-planetary-bio-surveillance-grid"/>
    <published>2025-09-01T14:57:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3232</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-08-28 01:28:38+00:00 (#3232)</title>

    <content type="html">Microbial Biofeudalism
The Reclassification of Microbial Life as Infrastructure (Part Two of a Three-Part Series)

We are witnessing the global implementation of a framework that legislates, regulates, and funds the replacement of natural microbiology with a synthetic, engineered, mass-produced, programmable infrastructure. This isn’t theory or future tripping—it’s happening now.

The human microbiome, inherited from birth to birth across generations of our ancestors, will be irrecoverably lost, as Bayer’s CRISPR creations dominate. Once replaced, the microbes with whom we have co-evolved for millions of years cannot be restored. In a very real sense, a part of ourselves is being erased.

https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/microbial-biofeudalism

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3232"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/microbial-biofeudalism"/>
    <published>2025-08-28T01:28:38+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3231</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-08-26 19:12:53+00:00 (#3231)</title>

    <content type="html">The World Microbiome Partnership (WMP) is an international forum founded in 2023 with funding from the EU Horizon 2020 to create a governance structure for microbiome manipulation across agriculture, medicine, and climate policy.

The WMP is aligned with the One Health and Planetary Health agendas (the same ones behind both the EAT-Lancet commissions "Planetary Health Diet" and the UN's Food Systems Summit that promises to eliminate animal agriculture).

WMP participants include the WHO, the CDC, NIH, and biotech firms.  They promote the idea that microbial communities must be governed like other strategic assets.

The key thing to understand is that the technocrats are reframing the microbiome as critical infrastructure: more like an energy grid or communication network than a sacred, living ecosystem.

As biotech companies deploy platforms to build GMO microbes to do everything from "manufacturing", to  biomarkers, to surveillance — the WMP seeks control of these novel systems, positioning microbial life as programmable, governable...and ultimately weaponizable.

- @iceagefarmer

[ This is part two of the investigation — if you’ve been following, you know where this is going. If not—buckle up... ]</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3231"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://worldmicrobiomepartnership.org/"/>
    <published>2025-08-26T19:12:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3230</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-08-25 20:12:05+00:00 (#3230)</title>

    <content type="html">It's uncanny the similarities I'm finding between the setup for COVID/mRNA and these GMO microbes:

- EUAs (Emergency Use Authorizations) being used to deploy without oversight/regulation (GMO microbes spliced with spider DNA to produce venom as insecticide. for real.)
- Pesticide Liability Shield going into place (like Vaccine Liability Shield)
- Giant Palantir-linked, WEF-partnered companies claiming they have a "microbe platform" — just as we heard Albert Bourla claim mRNA was a "platform" — to get cells to produce anything, not just spike protein!
- All of it actively hijacking biology to create infrastructure that feeds data to the beast system

I'm writing up everything as quickly as I can.  Part One on the replacement of natural soil biome with GMO Microbes is here.

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3230"/>
    <published>2025-08-25T20:12:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3229</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-08-25 20:05:39+00:00 (#3229)</title>

    <content type="html">ALERT: Pesticide Liability Shield !

Legislation has passed in 2 states and is being rushed through legislatures in 7 others which would create a "Pesticide Liability Shield."

This "liability shield" operates just the "vaccine liability protection" enjoyed by pharmaceutical companies.  If something goes wrong, you can't be held accountable.

It also applies to the genetically engineered microbes described here, so the name is a bit misleading.  It's more of a Biotech Liability Shield.

Understand that with this shield in place, "Big Ag" companies could knowingly do exactly what Pfizer executives were caught on hidden camera admitting:  develop a novel pathogen and a cure, knowingly release the pathogen, then "save the day" with their GMO product — and suffer no consequences.

- @iceagefarmer

#Biosurveillance #BiodigitalConvergence</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3229"/>
    <published>2025-08-25T20:05:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3228</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-08-25 19:54:54+00:00 (#3228)</title>

    <content type="html">Reformatting the Earth:  The Biotech Coup

There is an active effort to modify the substrate of life on our planet: to recolonize the very soil on the surface of the Earth with genetically engineered microbes — but there are risks.

Millions of acres of U.S. farmland have already been inoculated with with these GE microbes, replacing the ecosystem’s natural microbiome.  Containment is impossible, and remediation is completely unexplored.

And, this sets the stage for a planetary-scale biosurveillance apparatus.  Learn more:

FULL ARTICLE:  https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/reformatting-earth-the-biotech-coup

- @iceagefarmer

#BiodigitalConvergence #Biosurveillance #WarOnFarms</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3228"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://open.substack.com/pub/unshadowed/p/reformatting-earth-the-biotech-coup?r=5ur0io&amp;utm_campaign=post&amp;utm_medium=web&amp;showWelcomeOnShare=true"/>
    <published>2025-08-25T19:54:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3227</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-08-24 21:03:19+00:00 (#3227)</title>

    <content type="html">What do you suppose Gingko Bioworks' CEO means when he says American farmland is an untapped manufacturing base "for more than just our food production?"

HINT:  he's not talking about companion plants.

Full report coming soon.

#BiodigitalSurveillance</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3227"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3227.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-08-24T21:03:19+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3226</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-08-22 10:39:31+00:00 (#3226)</title>

    <content type="html">Researchers at UCSF recently disabled a gene in mice that controls "AMCase," the enzyme that breaks down chitin (found in insect protein). Without AMCase, the mice developed inflammation, lung disease and died UNLESS researchers "reverted" the genetic change or fed AMCase nasally.

The WEF has been pushing insect protein (Eat ze bugs!), and over the past few years, it has quietly entered the corporate food supply across the EU and even US.

When we see gene-altering mRNA now in pharmaceuticals and even food (see Terrana!), and chitin increasingly being added to the food, it's worth asking, with some high-octane speculation:

- Is FOOD being used to deliver a binary weapon in the depopulation agenda?

- Is chitin being introduced into the food supply precisely as human biology is being re-engineered to make it an even more potent toxin?

It sounds wild, but then, crazy proposals, like WEF-linked "bioethicist" Matthew Liao suggestion to engineer TINY humans to be allergic to MEAT to reduce our carbon footprint, reveal the technocrats really do think this way.

If the food supply is being weaponized against us, there is no better time to start gardening, raising animals, and returning to nature and truly regenerative solutions -- and I mean real ones, not the WEF's CRISPR-fueled biodigital convergence dressed up as sustainability.

- @iceagefarmer

#FoodWars #EatZeBugs #chitin</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3226"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://morningsignout.com/chitin-is-bad-for-lungs/"/>
    <published>2025-08-22T10:39:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3225</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-08-22 09:53:55+00:00 (#3225)</title>

    <content type="html">Nova Scotia's closure of forest land -- and excessive fines, exceeding $30,000 for just walking on public land! -- has raised eyebrows, and brings to mind the system's stated intention to impose CLIMATE LOCKDOWNs reminiscent of the COVID response. The goal is to paint nature as dangerous and full of zoonotic threats.  Fundamentally, it fosters the perception that humans are separate from nature and must be kept apart from it.

Nova Scotia is not alone:  this year, wildfires broke out across the Balkans prompting forced evacuations in Montenegro &amp; Albania, and causing forest and road closures also in Serbia, Greece, &amp; Turkey.

Remember:
"The wildfires are going to continue to get worse -- it will make believers out of even the staunchest deniers of climate change."

   — Jerry Brown during the Paradise fires:

They are delivering on their promise.

Expect to see more government-imposed restrictions on movement and access under the guise of "saving the environment."

#ClimateLockdown</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3225"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3225.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-08-22T09:53:55+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3224</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-08-16 11:23:42+00:00 (#3224)</title>

    <content type="html">California farmers left high &amp; dry as PG&amp;E (with Gov. Newsom's approval) CUTS OFF WATER to generational farms &amp; ranches, in order to "protect salmon."

“This happened two months before harvest,” "We’re looking at having to go out of business,” says cattle rancher Bernie Eckels.

Newsom also authorized the draining of Lake Pillsbury reservoir, causing wells to run dry, and depleting the water used for FIREFIGHTING — just like before the Palisades Fire!

“When they cut the river flow, they totally reneged on our water rights,” he says. “There are 65 appropriative water rights from the powerhouse discharge to Lake Mendocino. PG&amp;E’s arbitrary cut wiped them out.”

“Without water to irrigate our fields and recharge our groundwater, we’ll lose our ability to produce hay and our best grazing ground,” he says. “We’ll lose the ability to provide great local beef and lamb to our community.”

And that, my friends, is precisely the point.

#WarOnFarms

https://www.americaunwon.com/p/this-shuts-us-down-potter-valley</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3224"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.americaunwon.com/p/this-shuts-us-down-potter-valley"/>
    <published>2025-08-16T11:23:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3223</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-08-08 21:47:12+00:00 (#3223)</title>

    <content type="html">"People may not like fake meat, but they'll feed it to their dogs."

Meatly raising $27m to "prove Fake Meat pet food can be mass market.”

“We’re just doing chicken cells with a very robust cell line that we don’t need to genetically engineer to immortalize [keep dividing indefinitely], so it has great nutrition and great taste with a chicken pate-like consistency."

But hey, the UN was calling for people to kill their pets to save the carbon footprint, so maybe this is more humane? 🤮

#WarOnMeat

https://agfundernews.com/meatly-ceo-on-cultivated-petfood-we-want-to-prove-this-can-be-mass-market</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-08.html#3223"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://agfundernews.com/meatly-ceo-on-cultivated-petfood-we-want-to-prove-this-can-be-mass-market"/>
    <published>2025-08-08T21:47:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3222</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-07-24 10:40:17+00:00 (#3222)</title>

    <content type="html">Ground beef prices reach record highs as warning issued

Ground beef prices across the U.S. continue to reach new highs, driven by shrinking cattle herds, with looming import restrictions threatening to push costs even higher.

According to government data released last week, the average price of a pound of 100 percent ground beef rose to $6.12 last month, up from $5.98 in May and $5.47 in June 2024. Experts have said this trend shows no signs of slowing, meaning there may be upward pressure on prices through 2026 and beyond.

"It might be at least two to three years before we would see any significant change on the supply side that would ultimately lead to some moderation in beef prices," agricultural economist Derrell Peel told Newsweek.

#WarOnMeat

https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/ground-beef-prices-reach-record-highs-as-warning-issued/ar-AA1IZkKF?ocid=entnewsntp&amp;pc=U531&amp;cvid=7da36164d8f042f5b42ad62fb233a785&amp;ei=27</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3222"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/ground-beef-prices-reach-record-highs-as-warning-issued/ar-AA1IZkKF?ocid=entnewsntp&amp;pc=U531&amp;cvid=7da36164d8f042f5b42ad62fb233a785&amp;ei=27"/>
    <published>2025-07-24T10:40:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3221</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-07-20 00:31:12+00:00 (#3221)</title>

    <content type="html">[VIDEO] Moderna Founder Launches Aerial-spraying of RNA to Alter Gene Expression of Crops

You’ve heard of Moderna. Now meet Terrana.

Flagship Pioneering, creator of Moderna (and a WEF partner), has just unveiled Terrana Biosciences, providing $50mm to scale-up development of their flagship product, an RNA spray which enters the plant and alters gene expression.

“After being sprayed on, the RNA enters the plant through small tears in the leaves. With this method, Terrana can load in RNAs that act as ‘programmable plant vaccines’ or proteins that can aid in insect resistance or antifungal capabilities, for example.”

What’s more: the changes are hereditary. They flow to the next generation of crops.

So, the same forces who sought to modify the human genome, have targeted also our food and plants, as they mumble something about "save crops because global warming and cow farts."

VIDEO:  https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/moderna-founder-launches-aerial-spraying

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3221"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3221.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-07-20T00:31:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3220</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-07-19 07:50:10+00:00 (#3220)</title>

    <content type="html">UK:  Top farmland being "lost" to large-scale solar panels

England is losing some of its best farmland to solar panels, with nearly two-thirds of mega solar farms now built on productive agricultural land, a new report reveals.

The analysis shows that 59% of the country’s 38 operational solar developments are situated on farmland, with 31% of the total land covered by panels classed as the ‘best and most versatile’ (BMV) for agriculture—Grades 1 to 3a.

[IAF: This is the deliberate destruction of the UK's food supply, forcing the issue of lab-grown meat and mRNA-infused crops, in the name of achieving Zero Carbon]

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3220"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.farminguk.com/news/top-farmland-being-lost-to-large-scale-solar-panels-report-warns_66887.html"/>
    <published>2025-07-19T07:50:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3219</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-07-18 23:55:56+00:00 (#3219)</title>

    <content type="html">❗️mRNA for Crops:  Terrana

Flagship Pioneering, creator of Moderna, has just unveiled Terrana Biosciences,  providing $50mm to scale-up development of their flagship product, an RNA spray which enters the plant and alters gene expression.

“The difference with Terrana’s technology is it actually goes inside the plant. That really lets you think about solving problems differently.”  [Remember this rhetoric before from Bourla and Moderna?]

Their PR example is fruit trees that need sufficiently cold winters to flower and fruit:  "With Terrana’s product, we could go in during the summer, spray these plants to turn that requirement down, and we restore those orchards to productivity during warm winters," they say. "This gives us a little bit more of a buffer to work with them as we try to find more permanent solutions to climate change.”

But proof of concept crops already include tomatoes, corn, soy "and a pipeline of more products in specialty and row crops."

Naturally, no public safety trials have been conducted.

So, the same forces who sought to modify the human genome, have targeted also our food and plants, as they mumble something about "crop protection for global warming."

"no flesh would be saved..."

-@iceagefarmer

LINK: https://agfundernews.com/flagship-pioneerings-new-rna-based-crop-protection-company-could-provide-a-huge-way-to-deal-with-climate-change</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3219"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://agfundernews.com/flagship-pioneerings-new-rna-based-crop-protection-company-could-provide-a-huge-way-to-deal-with-climate-change"/>
    <published>2025-07-18T23:55:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3218</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-07-18 22:55:34+00:00 (#3218)</title>

    <content type="html">AI Helps To Create Lab-Grown Meat

[Forbes] AI is helping scientists to come up with more efficient practices for lab-grown meat.  From modeling in vitro processes and growth factors to simulations that model how “assessing mutant growth factors with the best binding energy” can help increase growth factor activity from 6% to 14%.

“This represents a major shift in solving issues surrounding greenhouse gas emissions, food waste, and animal disease,” she said. “Our solution is truly: winner, winner, chicken for dinner.”

IAF:  As always, the same strawman: appeal to the problems created by nasty industrial agriculture, and rather than suggest a renewal of regenerative agriculture, "fail forward" into AI food tech. 🤮

Shout out to all the REAL INTELLIGENT folks making REAL MEAT by raising their own birds and livestock!

- @iceagefarmer

#WarOnMeat

https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnwerner/2025/02/07/ai-helps-to-create-lab-grown-meat/</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3218"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnwerner/2025/02/07/ai-helps-to-create-lab-grown-meat/"/>
    <published>2025-07-18T22:55:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3217</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-07-17 21:05:45+00:00 (#3217)</title>

    <content type="html">Is Methylene Blue neurotoxic?

Everyone is talking up this blue dye, from RFK Jr. to Rogan to Alex Jones (selling his own brand), to the CIA-linked Wellness Company's Peter McCullough.

Wouldn't it be a crazy psyop if, after part the population injected mRNA, another part—convinced by "RFK did it" and Roseanne Barr tripping out on it—ran to ingest a blue dye that destroyed their minds?  ("Reducing dendritic arbor," means less connections between neurons, means your brain no work as good).

(It also affects your fertility, gentlemen!)

I know this was pushed out during the honeymoon period's weird wave of trust for "MAHA heroes," but perhaps it's worth asking before everyone melts their brain (and their balls).

There is no magical substitute for good exercise, real food, and restful sleep.

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3217"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3217.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-07-17T21:05:45+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3216</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-07-13 12:28:24+00:00 (#3216)</title>

    <content type="html">"Daddy Trump" now referring to MAGA as "his boys and girls."

Are you seeing the deliberate invocation of this "paternal" language as the Savior morphs into the Dark Father ?

Daddy's getting mad...

READ MORE: https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/daddy-trump-as-the-dark-father</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3216"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3216.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-07-13T12:28:24+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3215</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-07-12 01:40:09+00:00 (#3215)</title>

    <content type="html">"Daddy Trump" as the Dark Father

The man who was once cast as the Savior has now flipped to the Dark Father. The very character summoned up to drain the swamp is now not just shielding the corruption but even denying that it exists!

This is not a political event, it is one within the psyche...

As always, the ouroboros has turned inward, hungrily eyeing its own tail…

- @iceagefarmer

👉  https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/daddy-trump-as-the-dark-father</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3215"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/daddy-trump-as-the-dark-father"/>
    <published>2025-07-12T01:40:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3214</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-07-05 11:27:20+00:00 (#3214)</title>

    <content type="html">Sometimes, the mask slips, and rather than a plan or agenda, we glimpse the story that the empire tells itself.

Alex Karp, CEO of Palantir, offered such a moment recently.

👉 https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/they-need-to-wake-up-scared</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3214"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/they-need-to-wake-up-scared"/>
    <published>2025-07-05T11:27:20+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3213</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-07-04 21:25:35+00:00 (#3213)</title>

    <content type="html">Yanis Varoufakis (former Greek Minister of Finance) describes AI as a new form of capital that produces not goods, but behavioral modification.  This is achieved by engineering perceptions.

The answers provided by ChatGPT, or the images rendered by StableDiffusion — as these increasingly inform our perceptions, they in turn define the reality we experience.

This is what makes AI so powerful — he who controls the AI, defines the reality of tomorrow.</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3213"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3213.mp4"/>
    <published>2025-07-04T21:25:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3212</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-07-04 21:17:07+00:00 (#3212)</title>

    <content type="html">To my friends in the USA: Happy Independence Day.

May your efforts to build new families and communities be fruitful!</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-07.html#3212"/>
    <published>2025-07-04T21:17:07+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3211</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-26 00:10:40+00:00 (#3211)</title>

    <content type="html">Boy that didn't take long. 😆

Even my 30s "thank you" video was enough to get a new channel terminated from YouTube.

This is not just "censorship" — it is a new form of "curating reality." Defining who exists and what thoughts will be allowed in the future.  Purging undesirables from the dataset on which AI models are trained.  And thinking outside the box makes you persona non grata ...

Here's the video on substack.  Pretty dangerous stuff.

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3211"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3211.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-06-26T00:10:40+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3210</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-25 20:17:32+00:00 (#3210)</title>

    <content type="html">Thank you for the warm welcome back!  🙏

Side note: I’m honored to be among so many questioning and critically thinking friends who demand a "proof of life" video!! ;-)

Story here:
👉 https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/what-happened-to-ice-age-farmer

https://UNSHADOWED.org

X: https://x.com/UnshadowedShow
Telegram: https://t.me/iceagefarmer
YouTube: https://youtube.com/@UnshadowedShow
Bitchute: http://bitchute.com/iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3210"/>
    <published>2025-06-25T20:17:32+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3209</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-24 22:13:40+00:00 (#3209)</title>

    <content type="html">What Happened to Ice Age Farmer?

It’s true — YouTube removed the channel.  But that is only part of the story. Today, I want to share with you one of the responses to my work as Ice Age Farmer, which flowed through an interesting series of events.

👉  https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/what-happened-to-ice-age-farmer

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3209"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/what-happened-to-ice-age-farmer"/>
    <published>2025-06-24T22:13:40+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3208</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-23 19:49:24+00:00 (#3208)</title>

    <content type="html">After an hour, with N=700 votes on the poll, 50% are expecting more fireworks.  13% think T has outmaneuvered Netanyahu to secure peace.  37% are undecided — and 13 🥱's are too busy with their chickens to care [😂].

👉 Remember, in 2009 the Brookings Institute openly war-gamed a similar scenario using nuclear deals, regime change, and Israel as a proxy to start a war the US has long wanted.  As T escalates the rhetoric to "regime change" (destroying his own administration's credibility) and threatens Medvedev, it seems clear we're on an escalatory path, and these 'MAGA influencers' are either naive or disingenuous.

At any rate, I better go collect some eggs before one of my birds gets broody! 🥱</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3208"/>
    <published>2025-06-23T19:49:24+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3207</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-23 18:30:24+00:00 (#3207)</title>

    <content type="html"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3207"/>
    <published>2025-06-23T18:30:24+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3206</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-23 01:47:46+00:00 (#3206)</title>

    <content type="html">The closure of the Strait of Hormuz throws the global fertilizer market into a frenzy:  roughly 33% of global fertilizer exports—including urea, ammonia, and sulphur—pass through the strait.  For urea:

- Qatar (~13% of global exports)
- Saudi Arabia (~11%)
- Iran (~10%, and recently shut down completely due to the conflict)
- Oman (~8%)
- UAE (~4%)

In 2024 China slashed its urea exports by 83% YoY due to new export restrictions.

The net effect of these is that about 40% of the world nitrogen fertilizer supply is suddenly no longer available for export, which has traders at major importers (India, Brazil) panic buying to secure theirs.

Not only does this translate to very real impact on food supply and prices — it conveniently aligns with the WEF/UN agenda to "reduce nitrogen pollution..."

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3206"/>
    <published>2025-06-23T01:47:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3205</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-22 00:38:59+00:00 (#3205)</title>

    <content type="html">Ok, so the President of Peace just bombed Iran, hours after Putin said they are not evacuating Russian scientists.  Things are going to happen more rapidly now, and it's time to finish the preparations and brace for impact.

There is a non-zero chance that cyberattacks "by Iran" will take down the power grid and/or banking for parts or all of the US — soon.  Also, the media has repeatedly telegraphed the activation of Sleeper Cells which could achieve this or cause other non-trivial disruptions to life.

If you're new here, you need to at least have water, food and a way to prepare it for the events they have planned!

Here we go...good luck everyone.  🙏

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3205"/>
    <published>2025-06-22T00:38:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3204</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-21 20:10:52+00:00 (#3204)</title>

    <content type="html">Elon Musk casually announces he will rewrite history...

1737:  Andrew Ramsay "Freemasonry will furnish the materials for a Universal Dictionary ... By this means the lights of ALL NATIONS WILL BE UNITED in one single work, which will be a universal library of all that is beautiful, great, luminous, solid, and useful in all the sciences and in all noble arts. This work will augment in each century, according to the increase of knowledge."

1936:  H. G. Wells describes a "World Brain": a new, free, synthetic, authoritative, permanent "World Encyclopedia" that could help WORLD CITIZENS make the best use of universal information resources and make the best contribution to WORLD PEACE.

2025:  Elon Musk announces his AI is "rewriting the corpus of human knowledge" to "correct the errors."

History is written by the victors, and AI is trained on it.  (Yet another reason to train/use your own models -- #RightToCompute)

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3204"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3204.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-06-21T20:10:52+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3203</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-20 22:49:19+00:00 (#3203)</title>

    <content type="html">The Strait of Hormuz is not just an artery of the global energy system, it is also one of the primary paths in the global food trade system:

- Qatar imports 90% of its food, the bulk of it through the strait.
- Bahrain &amp; Kuwait are also reliant on food imports, depending heavily on maritime trade there.
- The UAE also imports a large % of food, much of it passing through the strait (although some could re-route to other ports like Fujairah)

- even Iran, ironically, relies on the strait, importing the bulk of its grains and sugar.

The grains mentioned above aren't just for people — it's also ANIMAL FEED.  In fact, the UAE, Qatar and Kuwait import nearly ALL their animal feed.

So, a closure of the strait—even for a time—could cause massively cascading problems, the loss of many livestock across the M.E., and spur a global food security crisis.

So ... how's your garden growing this year?  Now would be a great time to STOP depending on the system to feed your family.

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3203"/>
    <published>2025-06-20T22:49:19+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3202</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-20 22:27:23+00:00 (#3202)</title>

    <content type="html">Cold-Plasma Seed Treatment !

Did you know treating seeds with "cold plasma" can increase seed germination rate AND improve growth of your plants?

One of the first videos on Ice Age Farmer was on Cold-Plasma Treatment for seeds. I noted studies like this one that indicate treating seeds with electrically-generated non-thermal plasma can improve germination, growth rate, disease resistance and more.

Cold Plasma is like the gorgeous plasma bolts shooting off a Tesla coil—except it is generated in a special way such that the seeds won't burn.

Many cold plasma generators seem reasonably easy to create (especially DBD) — and I think there's a potential here to create something that could be used (even in off-grid setups) to help homesteaders improve their own yields AND offer a service (treating seeds) that they could provide in their area.

If YOU have experience generating cold plasma, I'd love to hear from you.  Send me a note:

iceagefarmer@protonmail.com

[ image via Plasma Channel ]

- @iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3202"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3202.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-06-20T22:27:23+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3199</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-18 01:40:07+00:00 (#3199)</title>

    <content type="html">This week has seen a massive acceleration in world events. It’s particularly surreal to witness the systems of civilization and the last vestiges of economic, social and geopolitical stability being finally fully dismantled before our eyes to make way for a new system. It is abundantly clear that there are no political solutions, and that neither strongman nor tech magnate can save us.

But it’s not just a man-made “poly-crisis.” When one throws in grand solar cycles, a pole excursion, a weakening magnetosphere, the possibility of a solar micronova, the irreversible sabotage being done to the human genome—just to name a few!—we see that humanity is really facing an “omni-crisis.” It’s like every red light is flashing in the cockpit of human awareness. To address this omni-crisis by encouraging steps we can take in reality (“So grow those gardens!”) is to understate the severity of the situation.

In deeply studying outward reality, it seems, there are no solutions for the problems humanity faces.

How do we respond to the omni-crisis?

➤ FULL ARTICLE:  https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/unshadowed  👈</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3199"/>
    <published>2025-06-18T01:40:07+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3198</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-17 02:26:30+00:00 (#3198)</title>

    <content type="html">Trump's post advising people to evacuate Tehran is more concerning even than the drastic movement of military assets, his dramatic departure of the G7 to assemble the National Security Council, and rolling out the old equipment for the USS Liberty/Lusitania false flag.

"Everyone should immediately evacuate Tehran!"

Remember when he posted "This is a great time to buy!" then pushed back the trade sanctions, causing the market to pop.  Later he shrugged, "told you to buy."

... "told you to evacuate."

Let's hope they don't execute this script.  But they may.  Now may be a good time to check your preps and top off your gas.

- iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3198"/>
    <published>2025-06-17T02:26:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3197</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-15 16:02:17+00:00 (#3197)</title>

    <content type="html">Facebook AI is the military now.

Detachment 201:  yeah, sure, a reference to a HTTP status code.  Sure this has nothing to do with other 201s, like Event 201...</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3197"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3197.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-06-15T16:02:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3196</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-15 14:52:03+00:00 (#3196)</title>

    <content type="html">Whoa!  New Hampshire's legislature has proposed a Constitutional Amendment protecting the #RightToCompute.  Check out the wording:

    the right of individuals to use computation resources shall not be infringed.

As I said, if AI (compute) is seen as the new class of weapons system (implying information is the modern space of warfare, as NATO acknowledges), then then the Right to Compute is just as fundamental a right as the 1st &amp; 2nd Amendments — and I LOVE that NH's proposed amendment reflects this by mirroring the language.

These people are literally trying to ban math.  "Too powerful, terrorists might use it."  Don't let it happen.

    RIGHT TO COMPUTE
SHALL NOT BE INFRINGED
                     🔥

 [read my full article here]

➤ NH Constitutional amendment (CACR 6) here:  https://gc.nh.gov/lsr_search/billText.aspx?id=828&amp;type=4

- iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3196"/>
    <published>2025-06-15T14:52:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3195</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-15 10:10:00+00:00 (#3195)</title>

    <content type="html">Side note:  Thank you genuinely 🙏 for the warm "welcome back."  I have heard the requests for a video, the questioning of whether this is an fake AI version of Christian, AND to learn whatever happened to Ice Age Farmer.  I dusted off my microphone last night and am working to post something real soon on that front.  (Or maybe I'm rendering a video of the AI Christian now..! 🧌)

But most importantly:  thank you, I sincerely appreciate it, and it's good to see you again too.
-
Find me on X:  https://x.com/UnshadowedShow

- iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3195"/>
    <published>2025-06-15T10:10:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3194</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-15 10:03:47+00:00 (#3194)</title>

    <content type="html">^ So, with all eyes on the fireworks over the middle east, the US military OPENLY merges with big AI.  (Or should I say "re-joins," since most of this tech came out of DARPA in the first place — but this represents a new level of defense/AI partnership).

Tell me again how AI is not a potent tool/weapon.  While the public is dazzled by explosions, the establishment rushes to strip us of our #RightToCompute, before anyone even realizes it's a thing.

"Computers for me but not for thee!" says Sam Altman, laughing...

#RightToCompute

- iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3194"/>
    <published>2025-06-15T10:03:47+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3193</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-15 08:51:36+00:00 (#3193)</title>

    <content type="html">NEW - U.S. Army swears in senior tech leaders from Meta, Palantir, OpenAI as lieutenant colonels to be part-time advisors.

https://www.disclose.tv/id/jbna6z7jcv/

@disclosetv</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3193"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.disclose.tv/id/jbna6z7jcv/"/>
    <published>2025-06-15T08:51:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3192</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-13 05:39:05+00:00 (#3192)</title>

    <content type="html">I actually have a strong aversion to AI; call me old school.  I like hand-drawn art.  I like hand-made music (OK, biased guitarist).  I worry about people who think they are falling in love with an AI chatbot.  And naturally I find it insane that the transhumanist elite intend to first use AI as a beastly control system, and ultimately merge with some "AI supergod."

But my own preferences had blinded me to this OPEN agenda to control all computational power on the planet.  They are OPENLY saying AI is too powerful for people to use.

Imagine if the ruling elite in 15th century Germany had tracked down Gutenberg and taken his printing press, with an old-fashioned Klaus Schwab proclaiming, “Mass communication is too powerful, we must ensure that the printing press is only used for social good.”  That's EXACTLY what's going on now.

The typical problem-reaction-solution social engineering script dictates that we will experience an “AI False Flag” which will be hugely damaging and scary. And then the politicians will point at it, and say “Ooh, big AI scary! We can't let terrorists have it. Thank goodness the WEF &amp; OpenAI already have these regulations on compute that we can just adopt.” The technocrats have their perfect technology, and we are FORCED to use ChatGPT, feeding their system.  Eat ze bugs indeed.

Having now seen the agenda, I have refined my thinking.  This technology must belong to all of us.  Whether or not we use it is personal choice.  Just as with the 2nd Amendment, not everyone wants to carry a firearm, but everyone should have the right to do so.

{
- Right to Free Speech
- Right to Bear Arms
- Right to Compute
}

If AI didn't pose a problem for the elite — they wouldn't be furiously working to keep it out of your hands.

LEARN MORE — FULL ARTICLE:

   https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/ai-decoding-the-psyop

- iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3192"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/ai-decoding-the-psyop"/>
    <published>2025-06-13T05:39:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3191</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-13 00:45:07+00:00 (#3191)</title>

    <content type="html">The idea that anyone could use powerful AI is not attractive to the powers that be.

Don’t take my word for it.  Here is Bill Gates admitting that “managing AI” is right up there in terms of importance with climate change, bioterrorism, and nuclear war:

Gates is not just winging it, these are highly intentional words, each with decades of planning behind them.  He is signaling the agenda to control AI. AI is seen as so powerful that it is a threat to the technocratic takeover. It can't be allowed in our hands. This is the new gun control.  AI is seen as the new weapon, and an informed populace therewith, a threat to the state.

LEARN MORE — FULL ARTICLE:  https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/ai-decoding-the-psyop

- iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3191"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3191.mp4"/>
    <published>2025-06-13T00:45:07+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3190</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-13 00:36:16+00:00 (#3190)</title>

    <content type="html">AI: Decoding the Psyop  [NEW (first) substack post!]

AI is powerful, and the idea that anyone could have this power is not attractive to the powers that be — it can't be allowed in our hands.  AI is seen as the new weapon, and an informed populace therewith, a threat to the state.   "AI Regulation" is the new gun control.

WEF, OpenAI, and others are rapidly moving to "regulate AI" by limiting access to compute capacity.  As they  build super-intelligent systems, they are simultaneously setting up the regulation to keep it only to themselves.

They will run realtime simulations populated by our digital twins, with perfect data on all resources from supply chain blockchain, to control their 4th industrial revolution. We will not be allowed access to any significant compute capacity. There will be no competing. There will be no innovating.

This regulation of compute power is the key that turns the lock on the technocratic prison.

So, why is there no “Freedom of Compute?” Where is the equivalent of an NRA fighting for the individual’s right to compute? We’ve never heard these concepts before, yet it is now equally important as the First and Second Amendment — where is the movement for a Bill of Rights for Compute Power?

I love humanity.  I love our art, our music, our spirit, our history.  I personally find downright distasteful an AI-created facsimile of truly inspired creative and intellectual work.  BUT — I will defend our right to use it.  This technology is here now; the bizarre but powerful genie is popping out of the bottle, and we must ensure no group claims exclusive ownership of it to control society.

The stakes are high here.  If we fail, we lose forever the ability to create our own models with real history, alternative viewpoints, alternative medicine, herbalism, permaculture, decentralized solutions, and we, and the coming generations, will be doomed to accept the already disappointing, disempowering consumerist technoserf rhetoric that ChatGPT or Grok serve up, sourced from establishment-approved sources.  We will live in reality dictated by Snopes and Wikipedia.

FULL ARTICLE:
https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/ai-decoding-the-psyop

- iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3190"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://unshadowed.substack.com/p/ai-decoding-the-psyop"/>
    <published>2025-06-13T00:36:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3189</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-06-11 21:31:49+00:00 (#3189)</title>

    <content type="html">Empty shelves are reported widely across the US, blamed on the cyberattack on UNFI (North America's largest food distributor).  Not just Whole Foods, as empire media is claiming.

If they are trying to really mix things up leading up to this Saturday's birthday military march vs. the growing riots — food shortages would certainly be a highly incendiary fuel to throw on that fire.

"What the Truck" covers the cyberattack here: https://x.com/FWwhatthetruck/status/1932875692964003976

Be ready for anything, my friends...

- iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-06.html#3189"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3189.jpg"/>
    <published>2025-06-11T21:31:49+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-05.html#3188</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-05-29 20:27:34+00:00 (#3188)</title>

    <content type="html">Years ago the WEF announced they would mess things up so badly that people would beg for AI to run things.  People were alarmed, and said "We'll never allow this to happen!  Klaus is evil!"

And yet, now some of those same people are cheering on Trump/Musk, hailing technonationalism, and demanding AI government, walking right into the digital convergence of the 4th Industrial Revolution...

It's pretty surreal — and it's a clear indicator that waiting for some strongman or tech magnate to save the day is not going to pan out.  Ever.  We each have to do our part of the work.  This channel is returning to look at what that work is, and how we do it.  Stick around if you want to save the world 🙏</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-05.html#3188"/>
    <published>2025-05-29T20:27:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-05.html#3187</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-05-29 20:13:34+00:00 (#3187)</title>

    <content type="html">👉 Find the correct group to discuss your topic or post your question! 👇

Ice Age Farmer solutions-focused groups where you can focus on Homesteading:
@IAF_Garden 🍅 Gardening, Main Group. 👉Join this one👈 regardless of which of these others you join!
@IAF_Seeds 🌱  Seed and rootstock information &amp; exchange.
@IAF_Birds 🐓 🦆 🦃 Chickens, Ducks, Quail, etc.
@IAF_Bees 🐝 Apiculture
@IAF_Rabbits 🐇 Rabbits: for meat, fertilizer, etc.
@IAF_Canning 🥫 &amp; Preserving 🏺
@IAF_Herbs 🌿 &amp; Healing ⚗️
@IAF_DIY Crafts 🛠 &amp; Land Search 👀
@IAF_Comms 🎙
@IAF_Baking 🍞 &amp; Recipes 🍽
@IAF_Mushrooms &amp; Mycology 🍄
@IAF_Homebrewing 🍺 &amp; Fermentation 🧀: Kimchi, Kraut, Cheese, Mead, Kombucha, etc.
@IAF_Goats 🐐 &amp; Livestock 🐄 🐑 🦌 Pigs, Cows, Sheep, etc.
@IAF_Homeschooling 📝 Home Education &amp; @IAF_Infants.

IAF news discussion &amp; channel comments: 🎢 @IAF_Chat 🎢. Your account must be a subscriber to @IceAgeFarmer, to post comments on this chat.

By your use, you agree: to the terms in that group's HELP MESSAGE. For detailed guidelines and assistance, read that group's message, pinned at the top.

👉 Find the correct group to discuss your topic or post your question! ☝️</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-05.html#3187"/>
    <published>2025-05-29T20:13:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-05.html#3186</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2025-05-29 20:13:21+00:00 (#3186)</title>

    <content type="html">*tap tap* is this thing still on? ;-)</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2025-05.html#3186"/>
    <published>2025-05-29T20:13:21+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3185</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-08 15:47:09+00:00 (#3185)</title>

    <content type="html">Spain's Largest Hydro-Power Plants To Halt Operations As Drought Worsens

#water #EnergyCrisis #eu

https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/drought-forces-one-of-spain-s-largest-hydro-power-plants-to-halt-1.1842645</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3185"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/drought-forces-one-of-spain-s-largest-hydro-power-plants-to-halt-1.1842645"/>
    <published>2022-11-08T15:47:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3184</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-07 14:35:08+00:00 (#3184)</title>

    <content type="html">DIESEL SHORTAGE: I’ve been hearing an increased number of reports of diesel outages.

It’s been spotty for the last few weeks, localized issues, but now seems to really be hitting home.

Above is Allentown, PA.

 What are you seeing in your neck of the woods?

Are they going to pull the rug after the election?

It’s a good day to top off tanks, charge batteries, rotate supplies, …

#usa #diesel #AbsoluteZero</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3184"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3184.jpg"/>
    <published>2022-11-07T14:35:08+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3183</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-06 15:43:58+00:00 (#3183)</title>

    <content type="html">UK confirms it will not insure ships carrying Russian oil (90% of insurers now)

The UK has gone completely mad, as the treasury has confirmed it will not allow any British insurers to cover ships carrying Russian oil from December 5.

By December 5, tanker owners that fly any European Union flag or carry P&amp;I insurance from an EU or UK club can no longer have crude oil onboard that originated in Russia, unless Russia has sold the crude to the buyer at or under a price cap pushed for by G7 members. The US is expected to join the insurance ban shortly meaning more than 90% of the world’s insurers will shun Russian-linked crude tanker business from next month.

[IAF: remember the #AbsoluteZero  plan was to eliminate shipping by 2030]

“We continue to stand by Ukraine in the face of Putin’s barbaric and illegal invasion,” UK finance minister Jeremy Hunt said

#shipping

https://splash247.com/uk-confirms-it-will-not-insure-ships-carrying-russian-oil/</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3183"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://splash247.com/uk-confirms-it-will-not-insure-ships-carrying-russian-oil/"/>
    <published>2022-11-06T15:43:58+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3182</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-04 14:54:54+00:00 (#3182)</title>

    <content type="html">Threat of a nationwide strike by U.S. freight railroad workers still looms...

2 unions have rejected a proposed deal with railroads, while 6 have approved it.

Others are still deciding, with votes of the 2 largest rail workers’ unions coming mid-November.

#usa #SupplyChain</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3182"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3182.jpg"/>
    <published>2022-11-04T14:54:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3181</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-04 14:39:06+00:00 (#3181)</title>

    <content type="html">“Global societal collapse “ warns 42-year old hedge fund with near perfect record

[So much for the soft landing.]

The world is “on the path to hyperinflation”, which could lead to “global societal collapse and civil or international strife.”

The firm, led by billionaire Paul Singer and Jonathan Pollock, told its clients that “investors should not assume they have ‘seen everything’” just because they have been through the peaks and troughs of the 1987 crash, the dot-com boom, and the 2008 global financial crisis, or previous bear and bull markets.

They added that the “extraordinary” period of cheap money is coming to an end and has “made possible a set of outcomes that would be at or beyond the boundaries of the entire post-WWII period.”

https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hedge-fund-giant-elliott-warns-looming-hyperinflation-could-lead-to-global-societal-collapse-11667470081</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3181"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hedge-fund-giant-elliott-warns-looming-hyperinflation-could-lead-to-global-societal-collapse-11667470081"/>
    <published>2022-11-04T14:39:06+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3180</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-04 14:25:51+00:00 (#3180)</title>

    <content type="html">Germany Backstops Commodity Traders as War Drives Resource Dash

[ IAF: This is basically akin to nationalizing the entire commodities market — so long free market as we dash towards #AbsoluteZero carbon agenda! ]

Germany is offering loan guarantees to commodity trading houses to buy energy and key metals, as Russia’s invasion of Ukraine sparks a global scramble for resource security.

Trafigura Group, the world’s biggest trader of copper, has already agreed to supply German customers with non-Russian metals for the next five years, helped by $800 million in bank credit that’s ultimately guaranteed by the German government. The trading house is now discussing a similar deal for liquefied natural gas, according to people familiar with the situation, and commodity bankers are pitching more deals that would have state guarantees to other traders.  [Yeah, I’m sure the bankers would love to pitch many deals with all risk pushed to sovereign! ]

- iceagefarmer

src: https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-11-02/germany-backstops-traders-in-war-driven-dash-for-commodities?leadSource=uverify%20wall

#EnergyCrisis #EU #Germany</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3180"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-11-02/germany-backstops-traders-in-war-driven-dash-for-commodities?leadSource=uverify%20wall"/>
    <published>2022-11-04T14:25:51+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3179</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-04 14:20:41+00:00 (#3179)</title>

    <content type="html">UK draws up emergency plan for extended blackouts and resulting crises, &amp; potential undersea cable attacks

The UK government is laying the groundwork for a "worst-case scenario" of week- or longer blackouts.

The “official sensitive” document warns any outage could cause “severe” knock-on disruption to food, transport, water supply, communications and energy sectors.

Plans include prioritizing access to food for the young and elderly, preserving two analog radio stations on backup power, and rationing households by “intermittent access” to grid power.

It could also apply if there is an attack from another state on sub-sea power cables. [!!!]

[IAF: do you have a backup way to cook/heat your home?]

- iceagefarmer

src: https://uk.news.yahoo.com/uk-blackouts-looming-heres-happen-155402344.html</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3179"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://uk.news.yahoo.com/uk-blackouts-looming-heres-happen-155402344.html"/>
    <published>2022-11-04T14:20:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3178</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-04 14:15:10+00:00 (#3178)</title>

    <content type="html">France trying desperately to restart nuclear reactors, but labor union strike delaying maintenace!

France generates roughly 70% of its electricity from a nuclear fleet of 56 reactors, all operated by EDF. However, many of them have been closed down for maintenance, some due to corrosion-related issues. Currently, only 31 units are reportedly operating. EDF has pledged to restart all shutdown reactors before winter to avoid power shortages in the country.

However, since October 6, there have been strikes among EDF employees involved in repair work at 19 reactors, delaying maintenance by several weeks.

Last month, the French national electricity grid operator RTE warned that it would not rule out the risk of blackouts this winter due to prolonged strikes halting the repair.

[this announcement, as it is revealed that UK was running drills about managing extended blackouts and resulting crises … it is clear what is planned for the #EnergyCrisis]

- iceagefarmer

src: https://www.bignewsnetwork.com/news/273030702/france-to-restart-nuclear-reactors---energy-ministry</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3178"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.bignewsnetwork.com/news/273030702/france-to-restart-nuclear-reactors---energy-ministry"/>
    <published>2022-11-04T14:15:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3177</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-04 13:57:23+00:00 (#3177)</title>

    <content type="html">Australia: flooding damages $150 million of wheat alone in NSW

Agronomists say the grain-growing hub of the north-west is expected to have "conservatively" lost more than 120,000 hectares of wheat that was nearly ready to harvest.

The region also boasts large barley and canola outputs and is in the summer planting window for crops such as cotton and sorghum.

“this ongoing wet weather with flood after flood after flood is just unbelievable."

Unbelievable losses, particularly when the world is already short on #wheat and other grains…

“There are many impacted farmers who will be cash poor and without an income as a result of this flooding, and that has caused widespread economic pain across rural areas,"

- iceagefarmer

source: https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2022-10-24/crop-flood-damage-estimates-north-west-nsw/101569484

#GrandSolarMinimum / #WeatherWarfare</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3177"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2022-10-24/crop-flood-damage-estimates-north-west-nsw/101569484"/>
    <published>2022-11-04T13:57:23+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3176</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-03 23:20:47+00:00 (#3176)</title>

    <content type="html">Further, search engines have devolved into curated sets of links — this was absolutely openly confirmed by WEF reps working with Google to override results for terms like ‘climate change.’ [video]

With curated search results limiting what an inexperienced user can find, and bots constituting 80% of the tweets on a given topic …

… the internet really is dead.

GET OFFLINE.  SPREAD THE WORD.  DECENTRALIZE.

— iceagefarmer</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3176"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3176.mp4"/>
    <published>2022-11-03T23:20:47+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3175</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-03 22:32:33+00:00 (#3175)</title>

    <content type="html">The system tried to front-run this with MSM talking points on a “dead internet conspiracy theory” that “feels real.”

It masked the literal deployment armies of bots across Twitter, telegram, any social network, comment section, reddit, /pol , etcetcetc

These bot agents:

- mix in poison pills to SIGINT by, for example, having bots yell “MAGA” or “go putin” in whatever channels they want to shut down.  (Later, big data analytics announce that all homesteading channels are putin supporters.  Seriously, there are Gates-funded organizations doing this, and they intend in the future to use these "associations" to censor any voice)

- Sway public opinion by appealing to basic crowd psychology (recall the ashe conformity experiments)

- annoy real users who are trying to find actual factual data

https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2021/08/dead-internet-theory-wrong-but-feels-true/619937/</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3175"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2021/08/dead-internet-theory-wrong-but-feels-true/619937/"/>
    <published>2022-11-03T22:32:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3174</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-03 22:24:53+00:00 (#3174)</title>

    <content type="html">MASSIVE ANTI-RUSSIAN ‘BOT ARMY’ -- 80% of TWEETS!!! -- EXPOSED BY AUSTRALIAN RESEARCHERS

An Australian university has unearthed millions of Tweets by fake ‘bot’ accounts pushing disinformation on the Ukraine war.

80 percent of tweets about the 2022 Russia-Ukraine invasion in its early weeks were part of a covert propaganda campaign originating from automated fake ‘bot’ accounts.

IceAgeFarmer note:  this is part of the “cognitive warfare” strategy that NATO openly discussed — next generation social engineering.  See my report here.

source: https://declassifiedaus.org/2022/11/03/strongmassive-anti-russian-bot-army-exposed-by-australian-researchers-strong/</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3174"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://declassifiedaus.org/2022/11/03/strongmassive-anti-russian-bot-army-exposed-by-australian-researchers-strong/"/>
    <published>2022-11-03T22:24:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3173</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-03 15:48:25+00:00 (#3173)</title>

    <content type="html">Look at that - US exports record amount of wheat in September (as other countries are stockpiling).

There IS no strategic grain reserve in the US - it was liquidated over a decade ago. Just like they’re draining the SPR now.

3+ mmt, to destinations China, Mexico, Philippines.

USA set up for incomprehensibly massive failure …

- iceagefarmer

#wheat</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3173"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/3173.jpg"/>
    <published>2022-11-03T15:48:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3172</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-02 13:58:57+00:00 (#3172)</title>

    <content type="html">US: Lawmaker warns of impact from diesel shortage, rail strike after election

Wisconsin Rep. Bryan Steil says that the economy could take a dual hit after the election if diesel shortages persist and rail unions strike as promised.

“weeks after President Biden told us that he had this all under control, and the trains would be running on time, We're now learning it's anything but that. It's another game where the Biden administration has kicked the can down the road and kicked it past this election."

Steil said the impact of the railroad strike could be exacerbated by ongoing shortages of diesel fuel, which power everything from tractor trailers to harvesting tractors.

"The shortages that we're seeing around the country is concerning," Steil continued. "But it's all the more concerning that we have policies coming from Biden and from Pelosi that are putting us in this position in the first place."

#diesel #EnergyCrisis #us

https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/energy/wed-wisconsin-rep-warns-economy-may-face-double-whammy-after-election-due</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3172"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/energy/wed-wisconsin-rep-warns-economy-may-face-double-whammy-after-election-due"/>
    <published>2022-11-02T13:58:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3171</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-02 13:51:54+00:00 (#3171)</title>

    <content type="html">Indonesia is stockpiling food RAPIDLY to weather this food crisis.

Is your nation? And if not:  Are you? How is the LOCAL food system in your community?
-
“Under a new presidential regulation, which took effect Oct. 24, Bapanas with the help of state-owned enterprises plans to secure stocks of 11 staple foods, such as rice, corn, soybeans, shallots, chili, sugar for household, cooking oil, as well as some meat and fish.”

Indonesia is striving to reach 1.2 million tonnes of rice reserves by the end of the year, enough to meet 3.9% of domestic demand, as it battles inflation.

#FoodPrices

https://www.world-grain.com/articles/17664-indonesia-building-rice-stocks-amid-inflation</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3171"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://www.world-grain.com/articles/17664-indonesia-building-rice-stocks-amid-inflation"/>
    <published>2022-11-02T13:51:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3170</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-02 10:28:54+00:00 (#3170)</title>

    <content type="html">UK: all birds must again be kept indoors as “We are now facing this year the largest ever outbreak of bird flu” and are seeing rapid escalation in the number of cases on commercial farms and in BACK YARDS —

"The risk of kept birds being exposed to disease has reached a point where it is now necessary for all birds to be housed until further notice.”

Animals are “dirty and dangerous” narrative sets the tone for end of ranching and forcing people onto fake lab-grown meat:

#BirdFlu

https://news.sky.com/story/all-poultry-and-captive-birds-in-england-ordered-to-be-kept-indoors-as-bird-flu-measures-stepped-up-12735094?dcmp=</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3170"/>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/media/https://news.sky.com/story/all-poultry-and-captive-birds-in-england-ordered-to-be-kept-indoors-as-bird-flu-measures-stepped-up-12735094?dcmp="/>
    <published>2022-11-02T10:28:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3169</id>
    <title>@iceagefarmer on 2022-11-02 10:26:43+00:00 (#3169)</title>

    <content type="html">Bird Flu: 1.1 million chickens culled in Iowa as autumn outbreaks begin

#BirdFlu

https://www.zerohedge.com/commodities/possibility-additional-outbreaks-bird-flu-strikes-iowa-egg-farm-million-hens</content>
    <link href="https://milahu.github.io/iceagefarmer/2022-11.html#3169"/>
    <published>2022-11-02T10:26:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
